It's your girl gangsta boo.
Right now we about to tune in to the boo lingo on Uproxx.
Remember if people say yeah ho,
it's definitely strictly aggressive.
We on your ass, so just know that.
Use it in a sentence.
Yeah ho, it's a statement.
When we say maim, maim, it could be multiple things.
We could talk about a person, place, or thing.
Use it in a sentence.
Maim, that felt good.
What's up maim?
So junk could be the same thing like a maim.
People, place, or a thing.
Can you use it in a sentence?
Oh man, that junk was fire.
Oh shit, we hit that junk.
Crunk is another word, a form of expression
of saying get buck.
We get buck in Memphis, we get crunk.
Use it in a sentence.
Crunk in your face.
We get crunk, we're having a good time.
What's up with it?
Meaning like, what's good?
It's kind of like, what up though?
Use it in a sentence.
What's up with it?
What's good?